Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org
["Spurs" playing]
♪ I'mma tell it like it is ♪
♪ I got a reputation ♪
♪ Don't underestimate it ♪
♪ You won't like the sting ♪
♪ Enter at your own damn risk ♪
♪ Ain't my first rodeo ♪
♪ If you wanna do-si-do ♪
♪ No tellin' what I'll bring ♪
♪ You better watch yourself ♪
♪ These boots could put you through hell ♪
♪ Better walk the line ♪
♪ One spin and them snake skins hurt ♪
♪ You might bleed ♪
♪ Don't you go and blame it on me ♪
♪Ha! ♪
♪ You better watch yourself ♪
♪ You don't wanna
You don't wanna catch these spurs… ♪
Wow. Look at you.
-[Alex] What?
-[Cole] You look like a real cowboy.
All tanned and rugged like that.
Whereas you look like
you stayed underground all summer.
Summer school didn't give me
a lot of time to work on my tan.
-How was Montana?
-[Alex] Good.
It was good. Learned a lot.
I thought Mom was coming to get me.
Something came up.
♪ Just when you think you're safe… ♪
Can we go? I haven't eaten since Wyoming.
♪ These boots could put you through hell ♪
♪ Better walk the line ♪
♪ One spin and them snake skins hurt ♪
♪ You might bleed ♪
♪ Don't you go and blame it on me ♪
♪ Ha! ♪
♪ Better watch yourself ♪
♪ You don't wanna
You don't wanna catch these spurs ♪
♪ A soul made of steel ♪
♪ A heart like a blade ♪
♪ A kiss that could kill ♪
♪ Just when you think you're safe ♪
♪ You better watch yourself ♪
♪ These boots could put you through hell ♪
♪ You better walk the line ♪
♪ One spin and them snake skins hurt ♪
♪ You might bleed ♪
♪ Don't you go and blame it on me, ha! ♪
[man] Miss Howard.
♪ You better watch yourself… ♪
So, how was your last day as an intern?
Uh, you a big shot lawyer yet?
Not yet.
Uh, these came for your uncle.
Is he still in Italy?
-Spain.
-[man] Ah, mm-hmm.
Oh, Miss Howard,
someone's here to see you.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hi, Jackie.
I can't believe this place is still here.
Your mom and I
used to come here all the time.
Did she ever bring you?
Yeah, when I was little,
we'd have milkshakes.
Katherine.
What are you doing here?
I mean, is everything okay in…
in Silver Falls?
[Kathrine] Oh, yeah.
I mean, everything's fine with us.
What isn't fine, Jackie,
is this.
Boarding school, Jackie.
Do you really want me to sign these?
-Is that why you're here?
-[Katherine] Of course.
I mean, I tried calling Richard,
but he's in Barcelona?
Has he been here at all this summer?
Off and on.
But Danny was here for a month,
and then there's the housekeeper
and Al, the doorman. It's been fine.
Jackie, if you wanted to stay here
in the city, I think I would understand.
-But Vermont?
-[Jackie] It's a good school.
And I don't know, I… I just thought
that maybe somewhere new would be good.
But I thought everything was going okay.
You seemed happy.
It was. I was.
Then… did something happen?
With Alex or… maybe somebody else?
No. No. I just… I just
had to leave.
I wanted to get out of Silver Falls.
I just wanted to go home, to New York,
to before… everything.
But this isn't home anymore.
I, uh…
I met some of my old friends,
you know, when I first got back.
But… everything's changed.
Our lives are just so different now.
And I tried to go to some places
that I used to go to with Lucy
and my mom and my dad,
like The Cloisters and Lincoln Center,
but it's just not the same without them.
[emotional music playing]
It just made me realize
that I don't belong here anymore.
I don't belong anywhere.
So… I just need to find somewhere new.
Start fresh.
Your mom and I used to come here
when one of us
was really going through something.
Like a breakup or if we flunked a test.
Although that was mostly me
because your mom never flunked anything.
And we figured out
that there was nothing we couldn't solve
without enough butter
and chocolate and talking.
I'm glad she had you to talk to.
[Katherine] I'm afraid
I did most of the talking.
Your mom was such a good listener.
They say you choose your family,
and Angelica and I definitely did that.
All of us, Jackie.
Me, George, the kids,
we still want to be your family.
Whatever happened, we can fix it.
We want you to come home to us.
I just don't know if I can.
Okay, well, I'm gonna be there
for you no matter what.
If you want to go to Vermont,
I'll just come see you.
I mean, who doesn't love
the Green Mountain State?
You do belong, Jackie.
With us.
["Birds of a Feather" playing]
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ Till I'm in the grave ♪
♪ Till I rot away ♪
♪ Dead and buried ♪
♪ Till I'm in the casket you carry ♪
♪ If you go, I'm going too ♪
♪ 'Cause it was always you ♪
[whinnies]
♪ And if I'm turning blue ♪
♪ Please don't save me ♪
♪ Nothing left to lose without my baby ♪
Never fails to confuse the defense.
♪ Birds of a feather ♪
♪ We should stick together ♪
♪ I know I said I'd never ♪
♪ Think I wasn't better alone ♪
♪ Can't change the weather ♪
♪ Might not be forever ♪
♪ But if-- ♪
[car engine stops]
It's gonna be okay. [sighs]
And if it's not, you tell me, okay?
Okay. [chuckles]
She say anything to you about coming back?
I haven't spoken to her
since I left New York,
but it's a good thing
she's here though, yeah?
Danny, can you give me a hand?
-[Isaac] Let's go.
-Jackie!
I want you to meet Gregory Peck.
Okay… Who? What?
It's his chicken.
I've raised him since a baby.
Chick, Benny.
-Gregory's a girl.
-Does it matter?
It does if you want some eggs.
All right, come on, guys.
Let's go. Come on.
Red, 60!
-[Jordan] Isaac, over here!
-[Benny] Come on, you guys!
[Isaac] Say hut!
Jordan!
[Lee] Let's go!
-Let's go, Jordan!
-[Jordan] Thanks, man.
[Isaac] Run! Run! Run!
[Benny] Jordan! Here!
[sighs softly]
[Benny] Jordan!
[Isaac] Outstanding.
-That's good.
-[Katherine] Hi!
Hey.
Oh, Jackie!
Oh, welcome back.
-[Katherine] Missed you.
-We missed you.
Thanks, George.
Hi, Parker.
Hi, Jackie. Welcome home.
It's good to see you.
Yeah.
You too.
-Hey, we'll finish later.
-[Parker] Mm-hmm.
Okay, I guess I'll go unpack.
[Katherine] If you need anything,
let me know.
Hey, how'd it go?
Well, she's here.
Did she say why she left?
Not exactly, but I think we both know
it had something to do with Alex and Cole.
Well, let's hope
they can all get past that.
I think I just need
to spend more time with her.
We'll keep an eye on her.
-We're gonna keep an eye on all of them.
-Hey, you want tea?
Yes, please.
I was going to send it,
but I figured I'd keep it here
for when you came back.
Thanks, Nathan.
[horse whinnies]
We really missed you.
Skylar too.
-How is he?
-You know, he's… Sky.
[chuckles]
And Grace?
Oh, we didn't really see her
that much over the summer.
Please tell me you brought back
those mini-babkas from Zabar's.
-They are hands down the best thing--
-The best thing that you've ever tasted?
Yeah, I know. [chuckles]
It's all he's talked about
since you got back.
-That's not all.
-Right, the movies at IFC.
How could I forget? And the eggs Benny
at that diner on 4th Street
and Jane's Carousel
and the Roosevelt Island Tramway--
It is really cool.
I didn't forget.
Thank you. That's awesome.
-Can I try some?
-No way. These are mine.
Wow. Well, I'm glad you're back, Jackie.
At least somebody can
I heart New York with him.
Hey!
-[chuckles]
-[Danny scoffs]
So, you miss it?
Yeah.
Yeah, I… I do.
But it's good to be home too, so…
Was Richard sad to see you go?
I guess. But he's been pretty busy,
so I know he's glad
I came here instead of Vermont.
And what about you?
Are you glad that you came here
instead of Vermont?
It's weird how familiar it is to be back,
but then it still doesn't feel like home.
Not yet, anyway.
You know, it was hard for everyone
with you leaving.
But everybody's glad you're back.
Everybody?
Yeah, some may take
a little more warming up than others.
It'll be okay.
[emotional music playing]
You okay, P?
She never even said goodbye.
She had her reasons.
It's okay that you missed her.
[chuckles]
Come on. Take it easy on me.
-[Parker] You're just mad that I'm better.
-[Cole scoffs]
[Parker chuckles]
[rooster crows]
[chicken clucking]
[horse whinnies]
Hi.
[Alex] Hey.
So, uh,
how was Montana?
Pretty much just like here.
Horses and mountains.
Alex, I, uh…
I got you this.
The guy at the bookstore said if you like
sci-fi fantasy, then this is the bomb.
It's a new series.
Uh, thanks.
I'm not really into fantasy anymore.
Alex, about when I left.
-I just want to explain.
-It's okay. It's fine. I know.
I messed up.
Shouldn't have, uh, said what I said.
-No, it wasn't because of that--
-[Alex] It doesn't matter.
You left, and now you're back.
[Jackie] Yeah, but--
Look, I really gotta put Murphy away
before school, okay?
Okay.
Alex…
Are we okay?
Sure. We're fine.
-Morning, Jackie.
-[Jackie] Morning.
Hey.
So, there's, um… there's toast.
-Thanks.
-And…
They moved Parker's football practice
to the community center park this year?
Yes, and it's at the same time as Benny's
swim class on the other side of town.
I can finish those.
-No, no, no. I got this. It's fine.
-Honestly, Katherine, let me help.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Please.
Hey, honey.
I have my Ag Soc meeting
today in Lockwood.
Okay, well, maybe I can
drop Parker off at football
after I take Jordan to the film club,
and then I can swing back and get Benny?
Benny's practice will be over by then.
You'll never make that.
-I could just bike over there.
-[both] No!
[Katherine] Why did they move football?
We made it work last year.
I don't know.
Sweetie, I don't know
if I'll figure this out by practice.
But they'll pick all the teams this week.
-Okay, who wants eggs?
-We will figure something out.
-[Benny] I do!
-[Lee] Yeah, but not too runny.
Excuse me.
[George] Hey, Cole, Danny,
can one of you guys take Parker
to her football practice later?
I can't. I have a study group.
[dish clatters]
What?
Danny?
I mean, sure,
but I'd miss the sign-up for drama club,
and they hand out
the scene partners today.
Oh, we need more drivers in this family.
-Hey, we will get you there.
-Okay.
I know. I'm gonna call Will.
Maybe he can get you there.
[Jackie] Guys, here's your lunch.
Okay, whose job was it to get eggs today?
-Not me. I did it Friday.
-Not me.
-I'm pretty sure it was Jordan.
-[Jordan] Shut up, man.
If you guys want to eat this morning,
somebody better go get more eggs.
And I gotta go. Bye, everyone.
I'll go.
[Cole] Need any help?
No. I'm good.
Thanks.
Jackie, can you stop for a second?
[emotional music playing]
I should get these to Danny.
Found it.
-Oh, thanks.
-Yeah.
Hey, make sure you water Friedrich, okay?
Friedrich?
-My ficus.
-Right.
But not too much. I don't want you
to drown him. I wrote it all down.
[Will] Got it.
Okay.
Phone, wallet, passport, boarding pass.
What's the matter?
-I don't wanna go.
-What?
No.
Of course you do.
Come on, a whole semester in Chile?
Up to your elbows
in soil for three months.
-This is your dream.
-[chuckles]
Come with me.
Hayles, we've been over this.
What am I gonna do
stuck on a biodynamic farm
in the middle of nowhere in Chile
while you work on your thesis?
Yeah.
Plus, I got the ranch development
to keep me busy here.
I know.
I know. You're right.
I'm gonna miss you.
Me too.
-It's not even three months, right? So…
-Yeah.
-You'll be back before you know it.
-Yes.
Well, unless I meet,
like, a hot Chilean farmhand.
-Yeah, don't do that.
-I don't know.
I'll make no promises. [chuckles]
All right. We should get going. Come on.
Okay. Hold on.
We have, like, 20 minutes.
[giggles]
[gasps] Oh my God, Jackie! Hi!
Oh, I missed you!
-Hi, Grace.
-It's been so dead here this summer.
I almost joined my mom's prayer group
for company. [chuckles]
-You didn't hang out with Skylar?
-Um, no. Not really.
He and Nathan have been
in their own little bubble of love.
You know? So I, um, helped out
at the church. I did a ton of babysitting.
I'm sorry we didn't talk
a whole lot this summer.
That's okay. [chuckles]
You could make it up to me
by telling me everything.
So what's it like being back?
Are you still with Alex?
'Cause everybody's talking about it.
It's complicated.
Complicated how?
Wait. Wait.
What?
He told me he loved me
at Will and Haley's wedding.
[scoffs] Jackie!
Oh my God! What did you say?
-Nothing. He had been drinking, so--
-[Grace] So you didn't say it back?
Well, I didn't know what to say.
Alex is so sweet,
and being with him was so nice.
But then Cole…
Cole what?
I found out he had fixed
Lucy's broken teapot.
He had kept it for me
since Thanksgiving. And then…
And then what? You made tea?
Like, come on!
We… we kissed.
-You kissed Cole Walter?!
-Sh!
Jackie, oh my God. But you were…
Weren't you still with Alex?
Does he know?
Wow, Jackie. That's--
I know. I know. I messed up so bad.
[Grace sighs]
So, are you with Cole now?
No. What? No.
Do you wanna be?
Grace, no.
And anyway, it doesn't matter what I want.
What's important is
making things right with everyone.
What does that mean?
What are you gonna do?
Well, first I'm gonna get into
driver's ed 'cause I need my license.
-I thought New Yorkers didn't drive.
-I'm not a New Yorker anymore.
Then I'm gonna have to
make things right with Alex.
Too mopey.
[rock music playing]
It'll be fine.
Sure it will.
[phone pings]
You've been doing that all morning.
Who is that?
-Danny.
-Danny Walter?
We've been texting
a little over the summer.
And what does his twin brother
think about that?
Ugh. The days of me caring
about what Cole Walter thinks
are well and truly over.
Hmm.
[Tara] Come in.
Jackie!
Oh! It's good to have you back. Come in.
-Thanks.
-[Tara] Sit.
So, you decided
against boarding school, huh?
The school requested your transcripts.
Oh, right. Yeah.
For the record,
I'm glad you decided to come back.
Silver Falls is lucky to have you.
-Thank you.
-[Tara chuckles]
Um, I'm a little late choosing electives.
Okay. Let's see here.
Um…
-Uh, yes. You don't have any.
-I'd really like to get into driver's ed.
Oh, I'm sorry, Jackie. It's full.
It's a super popular class.
Um…
The only elective still open is woodshop.
What?
Think of it this way.
The world will always need shelving.
So this is where guests will park,
then they'll walk to the yurts from here.
-And um…
-Can we get the yurts out--
We'll need more horses,
so larger stables at some point?
Although I guess we could hire horses
on an ad hoc basis at first.
We'll do the group cookouts here.
We have to get a liquor license.
And we'll do the dark sky tours from here.
Right. Um…
Well, hey, it's great. It's great.
You're obviously on top of it,
but can we get the yurts out
to the back field?
'Cause I don't want them there.
And, like, I don't know, dark sky tours.
Who's gonna do that?
I mean, you and I
know nothing about astronomy.
Yeah, we'll get help for that,
which is another thing we have to discuss.
Staff. We budgeted for two full-time,
but I think four makes more sense.
Four? [sighs]
Aren't we supposed to be
making money here and not spending it?
Or…
So, can anyone tell me what a lathe is?
No?
Okay then. [sighs]
A lathe is used to turn wood,
to make bowls, spindles,
legs for furniture.
Anything that needs to be rounded.
How did it go?
[Nikhil] Well,
as of next semester,
I am officially out of the job.
Yeah, Ms. Elson
is back from her sabbatical,
and technically I gave them notice,
so I'm on borrowed time.
But you have a job for now, right?
Part-time. I'm doing, uh,
freshman Drama and English Lit.
And I'm covering the newspaper club.
Well, that's something.
And who knows what can happen
in the next few months.
Look. [sighs]
When I turned down that job in London,
I was not expecting I'd end up unemployed.
Hey.
You're not unemployed.
Something else will turn up.
Hey, um,
you don't have to be
such a cheerleader all the time.
But… I… I believe in you.
And I know you're gonna do great.
Okay, um,
I'm gonna go, uh, set up
the newspaper room, okay?
All right, this is driver's ed.
I'm Coach Allen.
Find a seat, please.
Hey, Alex.
Can I sit here?
Sure, yeah.
Cool.
Driving, it's hard.
-It was great.
-[coach] You need to focus.
Yes, pay attention, please. It's day one.
Hey, you.
Hi.
-Hi, Olivia.
-[Olivia] Hi.
So… I want to join the paper.
What? Why?
Well, my homeroom teacher was saying
we need to have more extracurriculars,
and I kind of only have band.
Why the paper?
Well, I like writing,
and I want to get better.
And they wouldn't let me join last year
'cause I was a freshman.
But I thought maybe I'd have an in
with the new editor.
[chuckles]
The paper has to be really good this year.
I want to make it more serious,
do more in-depth pieces,
rather than just covering
football games and student council.
[Nathan] Mm-hmm.
-You want to see the first edition?
-Now? Sure.
-[chuckles]
-The school's had its budget cut by a lot.
And the arts are always the first to go
when money is tight.
Band, drama, after-school activities,
they'll all be on the line.
But I bet the football team
will be just fine.
[laughs] Hmm.
Wait, they won't cancel the fall formal,
will they?
I hope not.
But these cuts are a big deal.
I've done a special editorial on it.
Hoping to add it
to my portfolio for Georgetown.
Maybe I can help.
Be your unofficial assistant editor?
[chuckles]
You have a ways to go
before becoming assistant editor.
Oh.
Hey, if you're joining the paper,
I'm your boss, not your boyfriend.
Okay, boss.
[Skylar chuckles]
So, I'm in?
Yeah. You're in.
[chuckles]
You're so excited.
-I am excited.
-[laughs]
Okay, so you need to tell me
the difference between…
It's the first day.
You're supposed to teach us.
That's the whole point, you know?
What? You okay?
Yeah. I just didn't know
he knew Ruby that well.
-I thought you needed to get your books.
-I'll get 'em later.
♪ I'm still putting booze
In my apple juice… ♪
No, there's no way…
[overlapping chatter]
♪ I'm sad, I'm sad ♪
♪ Don't make me choose
'Cause it won't be you ♪
♪ I got no excuse, I'm bad, I'm bad ♪
♪ Ask anyone who knows me ♪
♪ Tell me not to, and I… ♪
[Katherine] Guys,
I just want to say how happy I am
that we're all here… together.
And Alex and Danny,
we missed you so much this summer.
Not me. I like the quiet.
[Katherine chuckles]
And Jackie…
we're so happy that you're home.
Yeah, I missed you, Jackie. Jackie's back!
[Katherine chuckles]
[all] To Jackie!
[Alex] To Jackie.
This is better
than boarding school, right?
[Isaac] What did he say?
[Nathan] She was gonna go
to boarding school?
Hey, can I be excused for a sec?
Um, sure. Until the food comes.
Thanks.
[overlapping chatter]
Hey.
Cole, great play you gave Isaac
on the field today.
-Mm, no, that wasn't me.
-[coach] Come on.
I know a Cole Walter play when I see it.
You know, if you're interested,
the assistant coach position
is still available.
Thanks. Yeah, I don't think so.
All right. Enjoy your evening.
[George] Coach.
-Good to see you. Bye.
-How are you?
[Katherine] Hi.
[chuckles]
Danny, what are you thinking?
-No phones at the table.
-Sorry.
He's been texting some girl back
in New York ever since he got home.
Oh!
-[Parker] Finally, some pizza.
-Good for you, Danny boy.
[George] Hey. Hey.
-Yeah, maybe later.
-[Isaac] Our boy's growing up!
-[Benny] The breadsticks will be better…
-If I did, I would.
Yeah. Thank you.
I gotta get strong.
♪ When everything feels like yesterday ♪
♪ Can't live with myself
I can't think of us ♪
♪ Find somebody else
I feel like I'm drunk ♪
♪ Tell me I'm right so I can stay away ♪
♪ Stay away… ♪
Hey, you need anything?
No, thanks.
You okay?
Yeah.
Just, you know,
adjusting.
♪ You see I'm lighting out your spark
And I'm leaving scars ♪
♪ I didn't mean to ♪
♪ Dancing with my fire… ♪
I don't know what happened to him
over the summer, but…
He's changed?
And not in a good way.
I've been texting this girl lately…
[cricket chirping]
[knock on door]
It's open.
Hi.
I thought I'd just check in with you.
I know today was a little tricky, huh?
[Jackie] Yeah.
I guess it will take a while.
And I tried to get into driver's ed today,
and it was full.
-You want to learn how to drive?
-[Jackie] Yeah.
I want to help you and George with
the younger kids and their activities.
Oh, Jackie, you're so thoughtful.
And yeah, it would be amazing
to have another driver around here,
but that's not your job.
You don't have to be useful to be welcome.
I wanna contribute,
be a part of the family.
[Katherine] You already are.
Listen, it was hard on everybody knowing
that you didn't want to be around us,
even for a little while.
And we get that you needed some space,
but some people are going to have
their feelings about that,
and that might take a little time.
And I'm sorry I made it seem like
it was gonna be easy to come back here.
It isn't.
And I see that now.
But if anybody can do hard things,
it's you.
[emotional music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
Hey, Brandon?
I was just wondering
if you'd switch electives with me?
Can't. I need my license
so I can help my dad with deliveries.
Hi, Maria.
I'm not leaving driver's ed, Jackie.
Uh, Jackie?
I'll switch with you.
Really? You sure?
I've got my bike.
I'll do it in the spring.
Thank you.
[Kiley] Yeah.
Oh.
Hi.
Hey.
Um, I… I didn't know
that you worked in here.
[Erin] Well,
just when Ms. Levin is shorthanded.
I like the quiet.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Do you need help finding anything?
No.
Hey, Erin, um…
I just, uh…
When I texted that I missed you,
I meant it.
So did I.
[emotional music playing]
Oh, hey, Jackie. Welcome.
We're working in pairs today,
just going over basic driving principles,
so just find a seat.
I want you to think
of a steering wheel like a clock.
-A clock tells you what time it is.
-Talk later.
Alex, you're late. Please, take a seat.
As I was saying, the rules have changed,
but one thing that hasn't is your safety.
Texting, putting makeup on,
eating, daydreaming,
all of these things can cause accidents.
[tools whirring]
Hey, um, Kiley, right?
How'd you end up in here?
Somebody let me down.
Uh, so this is a lathe.
And, uh, what you need to do--
Thanks. I know how to use a lathe.
Used it before.
Great.
You know you're holding it
upside down, right?
[scoffs]
Obviously.
Okay.
You're supposed to check
your rearview mirror and your side mirror.
Okay.
Did you check your blind spot?
[sighs]
-You left the handbrake on.
-Do you want to drive?
You two, you remind me of my grandparents.
Rest in peace, Gigi.
Alex, can we talk?
We are talking.
-I need to know what's going on.
-We've been over this.
I said what I said,
and you left without saying goodbye.
So it seems pretty clear to me
that there's nothing going on.
-Alex…
-But you're right.
We never did officially break up.
So if you need some kinda declaration,
let's call it now.
What?
Time of death, September 6th,
2:45.
Happy?
[emotional music playing]
-Kiles. Kiley.
-Where's the entourage?
Mm, uh, what?
Every time I've seen you
the past couple days,
you've been surrounded by your harem.
[whispers] I know.
It's insane, Kiles.
What's insane, Alex, is that
you would be so happy to become so…
I don't know, just like everyone else.
So what?
Maybe I am happy
to be like everybody else.
Maybe you should stop
trying so hard to be an outsider.
Maybe then you wouldn't be
so angry all the time.
I'm not angry all the time.
[Alex] Mm, really?
Then why'd you leave driver's ed?
Now I'm stuck with Jackie as a partner.
We signed up
for driver's ed together, remember?
-Yeah.
-[Kiley] Yeah.
And that first class,
you ditched me for some random girl.
-You mean Maria?
-[Kiley] Whoever.
The point is,
we were gonna do it together,
and now we're not.
Okay? And that's on you.
She asked to sit there.
I didn't think it was a big deal.
Yeah, you're right, Alex. It isn't.
[Alex scoffs]
[scoffs]
Oh, yeah. Not angry at all.
Parker?
Can I talk to you for a second?
I just want to apologize for leaving
and for not staying in touch all summer.
I really missed you.
And now that I'm back,
I'm really gonna try to be there for you.
And that includes
getting my driver's license
so I can take you
to football practice and other things.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
I'd be like your own personal chauffeur.
[upbeat music playing]
I… kinda missed you too.
Let's see it.
-Good try.
-It wasn't great.
[laughs]
[Kiley] Thanks, guys.
-See ya.
-Bye.
You hanging around
for more woodworking tips?
[chuckles] My dad's not really into
family dinnertime, you know?
Mm.
Only time he talks to me is when it's
about football and how bad I am at it,
and I just didn't really feel like
dealing with that tonight, so…
Ooh, sorry for the overshare.
-Um…
-[chuckles]
I'm sure your parents are great, right?
I live with my grandma.
[door opens]
D! You all on your lonesome?
Oh, just, uh, late-night munchies,
if you know what I mean.
Get me an extra hot pepperoni
with three sodas.
TJ, hey, just take it easy.
We close in 20 minutes.
We eat fast.
So you can read now?
Yeah. [scoffs]
-Academics. You know me.
-[TJ] Science?
Chemistry?
[boy] Pizza shredder.
Insert here, am I right?
[uplifting music playing]
[chuckles softly]
What's making you so happy?
Oh, nothing. Nothing.
So, um,
did you hear that Alex and Jackie
officially broke up?
So?
So, maybe you should go talk to her?
I just, um…
I know how much
she missed you this summer.
["Let It Happen" playing]
♪ No, I know… ♪
[horse whinnies]
♪ I'm a walking contradiction
And it shows… ♪
This was on the porch.
Mom said you were moving them into here.
♪ I'm aware that I could… ♪
[Jackie] Yeah.
It's time I made the room mine, I guess.
♪ But then we spoke ♪
♪ I had a backbone made of glass… ♪
Can you please stop running away from me?
♪ Now I stay up
And I wait here by the phone ♪
♪ If you're ready
All I mean is we could go… ♪
Don't go.
♪ I've never craved someone's attention ♪
♪ As much as yours
Thought I should mention that ♪
♪ I'd bet all my money ♪
♪ That I will lose to you
And hand you my life ♪
♪ Here's to hoping
You're worth all my time ♪
♪ I hope you're worth my time ♪
♪ I might barely know you
But still don't love you yet ♪
♪ But probably will ♪
♪ Turn me into something tragic ♪
♪ Just for you, I let it happen ♪
♪ I'd bet all my money ♪
♪ That I will lose to you
And hand you my life ♪
♪ Here's to hoping
You're worth all my time ♪
♪ I hope you're worth my time ♪
♪ I might barely know you
But still don't love you yet ♪
♪ But probably will ♪
♪ Turn me into something tragic ♪
♪ Just for you, I let it happen ♪
♪ I let it happen ♪
Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org